<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">experience-lib</string>

    <!-- Experience -->
    <string name="add_experience">+ Add Experience</string>
    <string name="add_experience_title">Select the type of Experience or import it</string>
    <string name="import_experience">Import from file</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning!</string>
    <string name="error_selection">The Experience you selected has already been added</string>
    <string name="understand">Ho capito</string>
    <string name="import_experience_error">An error has occurred during the import</string>
    <string name="quiz" translatable="false">Quiz</string>
    <string name="added_questions">Added questions</string>
    <string name="no_questions_available">There aren\'t questions here, add one by clicking +</string>
    <string name="puzzle" translatable="false">Puzzle</string>
    <string name="find_the_difference">Find the difference</string>
    <string name="diff_low">Low</string>
    <string name="diff_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="diff_high">High</string>
    <string name="diff_impossible">Impossible</string>
    <string name="difficulty">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="points">Points</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="time_invalid">Insert a minimum time of 10 seconds</string>
    <string name="seconds">Seconds</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="add_image">+ Add image</string>
    <string name="add_original_image">+ Add original image</string>
    <string name="add_different_image">+ Add modified image</string>
    <string name="select_difference_explanation">Tap on the image to select the differences</string>
    <string name="answers">Answers</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>
    <string name="insert_answer">Insert the answer</string>
    <string name="empty_answer">Answer missing</string>
    <string name="correct">Correct</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="questions_empty">Insert the question</string>
    <string name="points_missing">Insert a score</string>
    <string name="answers_missing">Insert at least two answers</string>
    <string name="correct_answer_missing">Insert at least one correct answer</string>
    <string name="incorrect_answer_missing">Insert at least one incorrect answer</string>
    <string name="questions_missing">Add at least a question</string>
    <string name="experience_saved">The Experience is saved correctly</string>
    <string name="experience_save_error">An error has occurred during the save of this Experience</string>
    <string name="image_cropped">The image will be cropped to make it square</string>
    <string name="grid_dimension">Grid dimension</string>
    <string name="puzzle_image_missing">Image is missing</string>
    <string name="insert_correct_grid_dimension">Insert a correct grid dimension</string>
    <string name="enable_rotation">Enable pieces rotation</string>
    <string name="difficulty_value">Difficulty: %1$s</string>
    <string name="points_value">Points: %1$d</string>
    <string name="exit_confirmation">Do you want to really exit? Unsaved changes will be lost.</string>
    <string name="yes_exit">Yes, exit</string>
    <string name="no_continue">No, continue</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="delete_experience">Delete</string>
    <string name="share_experience">Share</string>
    <string name="share_error">An error has occurred during the sharing</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete">Do you really want to delete this item?</string>
    <string name="yes_delete">Yes, delete</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="deleted_experience">Experience deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="deleted_question">Question deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="deleted_answer">Answer deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="experience_deleted_error">An error occurred</string>
    <string name="ftd_original_image_missing">The original image is missing</string>
    <string name="ftd_different_image_missing">The modified image is missing</string>
    <string name="ftd_differnces_missing">Select the differences between the images</string>
    <string name="find_rfid">Find RFID tag</string>
    <string name="insert_message">Insert your hint message</string>
    <string name="message_tooltip">The most famous painting of Salvador Dalì…</string>
    <string name="insert_rfid_code">Insert RFID code in UUID format</string>
    <string name="message_missing">Insert the message</string>
    <string name="rfid_code_missing">Insert RFID code</string>
    <string name="rfid_code_wrong_format">Insert a correct RFID code</string>
    <string name="rfid_list">List of RFID</string>
    <string name="pattern">Memorize the pattern</string>
    <string name="touch_dot">Touch the dots to specify a pattern</string>
    <string name="dot_number_error">Selected dots should be at least 3</string>
    <string name="choose_pattern">Choose the pattern</string>
    <string-array name="pattern_difficulty">
        <item>Level 1 - Easy</item>
        <item>Level 2 - Medium</item>
        <item>Level 3 - Hard</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="find_details">Find details</string>
    <string name="tap_to_details">Tap on the image to highlight the details</string>
    <string name="details_message_hint">Find the gothic columns</string>
    <string name="details_missing">Select the details to find</string>
    <string name="single_question">Single question</string>


    <string name="hit_the_enemy">Hit the enemy</string>
    <string name="difficulty_text_indicator">Difficulty: %s</string>
    <string name="character_name_empty">Character name is missing</string>
    <string name="character_image_missing">Character image is missing</string>
    <string name="background_image_missing">Background image is missing</string>
    <string name="enemy_image_missing">Enemy image is missing</string>
    <string name="enemy_hit_image_missing">Enemy hit image is missing</string>
    <string name="hit_the_enemy_created">Item created successfully</string>

    <string name="recognize_the_object">Recognize the object</string>
    <string name="reference_image_missing">Reference image missing</string>
    <string name="description_missing">Description is missing</string>

    <string name="questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="choose_questionnaire">Choose the questionnaire</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <!-- Experience help -->
    <string name="help_title">What is this?</string>
    <string name="ok_understand">OK, I Understand</string>
    <string name="puzzle_help">Make a puzzle! Upload the image using the appropriate button. Scrolling down you can decide how many pieces it should have through the size of the grid. Attention, the puzzle will necessarily be square! Finally, decide whether or not to enable the rotation of the puzzle pieces to increase the difficulty or not. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="quiz_help">The quiz is a series of questions to ask the visitor in a certain amount of time. Add as many questions as you want using the appropriate \"Add question\" button. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="question_help">Create your question to insert in the quiz and decide how many points it should be worth. Use the text field to write the content of your question and possibly also add an image. Enter your answers via the \"Add an answer\" button. You get to decide what to write and even if that answer is correct. You have no limit on the number of correct or incorrect answers. Save your question and go back by pressing the \"Save\"</string> button
    <string name="ftd_help">In this section you can make your own \"Find the difference\" game. First add the original image and then the one with the differences using the \"Add modified image\" button. Highlight the differences by clicking on the affected point of the second image. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="pattern_help">This game allows you to test the visitor\'s memory. Create a sequence of points in the grid below by clicking on the appropriate black point. The visitor will see this sequence for a few seconds and will have to reproduce it. By selecting the \"Load a pattern\" button you will be able to load 3 patterns according to 3 levels of difficulty. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="find_rfid_help">Organise a treasure hunt! This game allows you to use your smartphone as a metal detector to search for the right object, bringing it close to the RFID tag (a chip similar to the one contained in credit cards). To configure this Experience, just enter the message to be shown to the user and enter the RFID tag code. Alternatively, you can upload a ready-made code via the \"Upload RFID\" button. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="find_details_help">Test the visitor\'s detective skills! Enter a hint message and upload an image by pressing the \"Add Image\" button to start hunting for details. Indicate the details that the visitor will have to find, simply by clicking on the interested point in the image. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="single_question_help">In this section you can prepare a single question that the visitor will have to answer as quickly as possible. Write your question in the text field and click on \"Add answer\" to write an answer, deciding whether it is correct or not. There is no limit on the number of correct answers. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="hit_the_enemy_help">In this game the visitor will have to defeat the enemy by hitting him repeatedly. Your goal is to customize some mechanics and visuals of this game. As you can see there are some already ready for you and that the user can choose as soon as the game starts. You can also create new ones to make a game with the characters and settings of your cultural place. Click on \"Add a choice\" to get started. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience.</string>
    <string name="hit_the_enemy_item_help">Start building the game. Choose the name of the main character and also choose what appearance he will have by clicking on \"Add character image\". You can also change its movement speed. Also add a background and an enemy by clicking the appropriate buttons. For the latter you can also decide its resistance to blows to make it as strong as you want. Finally, also choose the shot that your character will be able to fire and its speed. Click on \"Save\" to save this choice.</string>
    <string name="recognize_object_help">In this game, the player will have to understand only from the description you provide him which object you are referring to and use the camera to figure out if the object is the right one or not. The artificial intelligence will take care of the rest. Enter a reference image of the object and possibly also the name of the AI model. Click \"Save\" to save the Experience. Click on one of the 3 to find out more details and read the questions.</string>
    <string name="sus_help">The SUS, acronym for "System Usability Scale", is a system usability evaluation questionnaire. It is used to evaluate the effectiveness, efficiency and user satisfaction in using a system. Click on \"Save\" to save this Experience.</string>
    <string name="sam_help">The SAM is a user experience assessment tool that uses stylized graphical representations of an individual to measure users\' emotional reaction to a product, service or experience. Click on \"Save\" to save this Experience.</string>
    <string name="nasa_tlx_help">The NASA-TLX (Task Load Index) is a subjective assessment tool that measures the mental workload perceived by users performing a specific task. Click on \"Save\" to save this Experience.</string>
    <string name="experience_help">In this Experience you can indicate the difficulty and the score to the user. Choose the difficulty out of 4 values: low, medium, high and impossible. Also decide the maximum score that the user will achieve upon completing this Experience.</string>
    <string name="timed_experience_help">In this Experience you can tell the user the difficulty, the score and the maximum time. Choose the difficulty out of 4 values: low, medium, high and impossible. You also decide the maximum score that the user will achieve upon completing this Experience and also choose the time. The score will vary depending on how long it took the user to complete the experience.</string>
    <string name="blocked_timed_experience_help">In this Experience you can tell the user the difficulty, the score and the maximum time. Choose the difficulty out of 4 values: low, medium, high and impossible. The maximum score will be calculated from the sum of the single scores of each question. The score will vary depending on how long it took the user to complete the experience.</string>

    <string name="msg_internet_non_disponibile">Internet is not available</string>
</resources>